<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--Changelog-->
    <string-array name="changelog" translatable="false">
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev23</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev22</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev21</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev20</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev19</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev18</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev17</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev16</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev15</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev14</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev13</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev12</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Points to the changelog of current version.-->
    <string name="release_notes" translatable="false">@string/changelog_400_dev23</string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev12-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev12" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev12)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n - Added Video Surface support.
            \n - Added support compact layout in support Console, new rich animations.
            \n - Major app <b>redesign</b> with improved performance and structure.
            \n - Updated app architecture and cleaned up legacy components.
            \n - Enhanced stability with improved <b>telemetry</b> integration.
            \n - Refined resource handling and UI text for a more consistent experience.
            \n - Implemented various <b>actions</b> for the <b>Videos Screen</b> to improve user interactivity and functionality.
            \n - Updated <b>Codex</b> to support a 16KB page size, ensuring compatibility with newer Android versions while enhancing overall performance and stability.
            \n - Added support for <b>Properties</b> dialog.
            \n - Fixed UI issue with <b>Slider</b>, it now animates correctly.
            \n\n - <font color='yellow'><b>Enjoy, and happy testing!</b></font>
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev13-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev13" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev13)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Fixed an issue where <b>scrubbing</b> could cause an <font color='red'>ANR</font> crash.
           \n- Fixed an issue where the <b>slider</b> would jump unexpectedly during seek.
           \n- Added support for displaying a comprehensive <b>changelog</b>, allowing users to track updates and new features.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev14-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev14" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev14)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Implemented an <b>auto-hide controller</b> for a more immersive video playback experience.
           \n- Introduced a <b>toggle for rotation lock</b>, giving users more control over screen orientation.
           \n- Addressed several <b>minor bugs</b> across various modules to enhance stability and performance.
           \n- Improved overall application responsiveness and fixed miscellaneous UI glitches.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev15-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev15" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev15)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Added <b><i>Like/Unlike</i></b> button in <b>Media Notification</b>
           \n- Added a <b>Lock controller</b> for the player controller when playing videos, preventing accidental interactions.
           \n- Fixed issue with <b>Next/Prev button</b> not updating after detecting their availability.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev16-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev16" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev16)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Implemented an <b>Acrylic effect</b> for the Console background, creating an immersive ambient lighting experience.
           \n- Resolved an issue with <b>state updates</b> that occasionally caused them to fail, ensuring more reliable UI responsiveness.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev17-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev17" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev17)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Adjusted parameters of <b>Acrylic background effect</b> for console, enhancing visual depth and clarity.
           \n- <b>Colorization strategy</b> toggle now switches between <i>default</i> and <i>wallpaper-based</i> themes, offering greater personalization.
           \n- Fixed an issue where the <b>navigation bar</b> was incorrectly displayed in areas where it should have been hidden.
           \n- Resolved a problem that caused the <b>Mini-player</b> to appear even when the <b>Console</b> was visible, ensuring a cleaner interface.
           \n- Introduced a <b>Queue Management UI</b> that intelligently adapts to screen orientation, positioning itself next to the player, similar to the YouTube application.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev18-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev18" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev18)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Integrated <b>Sleep Timer</b> functionality with a dedicated user interface and underlying logic.
           \n- Implemented <b>Playback Speed</b> controls, complete with user interface elements and operational logic.
           \n- Bug fix - Addressed an issue where removing the current track caused the player to play the first item in the queue instead of the next, improving playback continuity.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev19-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev19" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev19)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Added <b>Equalizer</b>; you can now adjust audio frequencies for a personalized listening experience.
           \n- Implemented <b>Presets</b> for the Equalizer, allowing quick selection of optimized audio settings.
           \n- Fixed an issue where the <b>Equalizer</b> settings were not consistently applied across sessions.
           \n- Resolved several minor UI bugs related to the <b>Equalizer</b> interface for a smoother user experience.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev20-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev20" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev20)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Enhanced <b>Media Management</b>: Added "Remove" and "Delete" options to the Media player screen. "Remove" takes a track out of the current playlist, while "Delete" removes it from the phone and playlist, potentially moving it to a trash folder if supported. Buttons have been updated for a better look and feel.
           \n- Smoother <b>Playback Queue</b>: Improved animation for currently playing songs in the queue.
           \n- Improved <b>New Playlist Creation</b>: The screen for creating new playlists has a refreshed look, adapts to phone orientation, features updated "Update" and "Save" buttons, and has an enhanced playlist description area.
           \n- <b>Audio Effects Screen Update</b>: The "Save" button on the audio effects screen now has a new design.
           \n- Clearer <b>Titles</b>: Updated titles on the "New Playlist" and "Audio Effects" screens for better descriptiveness.
           \n- <b>Settings Fix</b>: Resolved a minor issue with color theme settings to ensure proper functionality.
           \n- <b>Behind-the-Scenes Improvements</b>: Enhanced the functionality of the equalizer (sound settings).
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev21-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev21" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev21)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Added MP3 <b>Tag Editor</b>: View/edit metadata (title, artist, album, etc.). Adaptive UI; Pro features for lyrics/artwork.
           \n- Refined UI in the <b>Queue</b>: the currently playing item\'s title now animates its font weight.
           \n- Adjusted the <b>Acrylic</b> effect\'s luminosity alpha in both light and dark themes for better visual balance.
           \n- Optimized <b>Image Blur Transformations</b>: Improved bitmap handling for better performance and reduced memory usage.
           \n- Enhanced <b>LazyList Placeholders</b>: Full-screen Lottie animations for loading/empty states in vertical `LazyList` components.
           \n- Streamlined <b>\"Add to Playlist\"</b>:
           \n    - New playlist selection dialog (name, track count, date, artwork). Adapts position to screen size.
           \n    - "Close" button, tap to select, placeholder for no playlists.
           \n    - Consistent dialog in Audio/Video sections. Adds tracks, filters duplicates, confirms with toast.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev22-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev22" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev22)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- <b>Save MP3 Tag Edits</b>: You can now save changes to MP3 tags with a confirmation before overwriting.
           \n- <b>MP3 Only Edits</b>: The "Edit" option now checks if a file is an MP3, showing a message if it\'s not.
           \n- <b>Add to Playlist from Videos &amp; Playlists</b>: Easily add individual videos or tracks from one playlist to another.
           \n- <b>Improved Tag Handling</b>: Better reading and writing of common ID3 tags.
           \n- <b>"Liked" Playlist Title</b>: The title for your "Liked" songs playlist is now clearer.
           \n- <b>"Recent" Playlist Update</b>: Fixed a small issue to make sure recently played items are correctly added to the "Recent" playlist.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev23-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev23" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev23)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
          \n- Refined <b>Console</b> UI: Streamlined dialog management and introduced dedicated state for queue visibility.
          \n- Improved <b>Sleep Timer</b> Dialog: "Start" button moved to actions slot with updated styling.
          \n- <b>Widget Overhaul</b>:
          \n    - Introduced Close button for the widget.
          \n    - <b>New FAB Video Player</b>: A new floating action button style player for video content.
          \n    - <b>Expanded Widget (MistyTunes)</b>: Added a <b>Like</b> button with a Lottie animation. Skip buttons now use `TonalIconButton` and reflect availability. "Open Console" is now a `TonalIconButton`. Footer controls layout adjusted.
          \n    - <b>Compact Widget (FabPlayer)</b>: Updated to use new request constants.
          \n- Adjusted widget padding on the Home screen for better layout when the navigation bar is not visible in portrait mode.
          \n- <b>Dynamic Feature Module Installation</b>:
          \n    - Implemented infrastructure to install dynamic feature modules (e.g., "Codex") via the Play Store.
          </font>
    </string>
</resources>