<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev12-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev12" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev12)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n - Added Video Surface support.
            \n - Added support compact layout in support Console, new rich animations.
            \n - Major app <b>redesign</b> with improved performance and structure.
            \n - Updated app architecture and cleaned up legacy components.
            \n - Enhanced stability with improved <b>telemetry</b> integration.
            \n - Refined resource handling and UI text for a more consistent experience.
            \n - Implemented various <b>actions</b> for the <b>Videos Screen</b> to improve user interactivity and functionality.
            \n - Updated <b>Codex</b> to support a 16KB page size, ensuring compatibility with newer Android versions while enhancing overall performance and stability.
            \n - Added support for <b>Properties</b> dialog.
            \n - Fixed UI issue with <b>Slider</b>, it now animates correctly.
            \n\n - <font color='yellow'><b>Enjoy, and happy testing!</b></font>
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev13-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev13" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev13)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Fixed an issue where <b>scrubbing</b> could cause an <font color='red'>ANR</font> crash.
           \n- Fixed an issue where the <b>slider</b> would jump unexpectedly during seek.
           \n- Added support for displaying a comprehensive <b>changelog</b>, allowing users to track updates and new features.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev14-->
    <!---->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev14" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='yellow'>(v4.0.0-dev14)</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Implemented an <b>auto-hide controller</b> for a more immersive video playback experience.
           \n- Introduced a <b>toggle for rotation lock</b>, giving users more control over screen orientation.
           \n- Addressed several <b>minor bugs</b> across various modules to enhance stability and performance.
           \n- Improved overall application responsiveness and fixed miscellaneous UI glitches.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--Points to the changelog of current version.-->
    <string name="release_notes" translatable="false">@string/changelog_400_dev14</string>
    <!--Changelog-->
    <string-array name="changelog" translatable="false">
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev14</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev13</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev12</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>