<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--
        Changelog Version Color Coding Rules:
        1. Dev / Nightly : Crimson #DC143C    (Experimental builds, potentially unstable)
        2. Alpha         : Orange     (Early testing phase, features may be incomplete)
        3. Beta          : DodgerBlue (More stable testing phase, nearing feature completion)
        4. RC            : Purple     (Release Candidate, polish and bug fixing phase)
        5. Release       : Green      (Stable public release)
    -->

<resources>
    <!--Changelog-->
    <string-array name="changelog" translatable="false">
        <item>@string/changelog_400_alpha04</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_alpha03</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_alpha02</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_alpha01</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev25</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev24</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev23</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev22</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev21</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev20</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev19</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev18</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev17</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev16</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev15</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev14</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev13</item>
        <item>@string/changelog_400_dev12</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--Points to the changelog of current version.-->
    <string name="release_notes" translatable="false">@string/changelog_400_alpha05</string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev12-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev12" translatable="false">
        <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev12)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n - Added Video Surface support.
            \n - Added support compact layout in support Console, new rich animations.
            \n - Major app <b>redesign</b> with improved performance and structure.
            \n - Updated app architecture and cleaned up legacy components.
            \n - Enhanced stability with improved <b>telemetry</b> integration.
            \n - Refined resource handling and UI text for a more consistent experience.
            \n - Implemented various <b>actions</b> for the <b>Videos Screen</b> to improve user interactivity and functionality.
            \n - Updated <b>Codex</b> to support a 16KB page size, ensuring compatibility with newer Android versions while enhancing overall performance and stability.
            \n - Added support for <b>Properties</b> dialog.
            \n - Fixed UI issue with <b>Slider</b>, it now animates correctly.
            \n\n - <font color='yellow'><b>Enjoy, and happy testing!</b></font>
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev13-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev13" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev13)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Fixed an issue where <b>scrubbing</b> could cause an <font color='red'>ANR</font> crash.
           \n- Fixed an issue where the <b>slider</b> would jump unexpectedly during seek.
           \n- Added support for displaying a comprehensive <b>changelog</b>, allowing users to track updates and new features.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev14-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev14" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev14)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Implemented an <b>auto-hide controller</b> for a more immersive video playback experience.
           \n- Introduced a <b>toggle for rotation lock</b>, giving users more control over screen orientation.
           \n- Addressed several <b>minor bugs</b> across various modules to enhance stability and performance.
           \n- Improved overall application responsiveness and fixed miscellaneous UI glitches.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev15-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev15" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev15)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Added <b><i>Like/Unlike</i></b> button in <b>Media Notification</b>
           \n- Added a <b>Lock controller</b> for the player controller when playing videos, preventing accidental interactions.
           \n- Fixed issue with <b>Next/Prev button</b> not updating after detecting their availability.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev16-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev16" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev16)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Implemented an <b>Acrylic effect</b> for the Console background, creating an immersive ambient lighting experience.
           \n- Resolved an issue with <b>state updates</b> that occasionally caused them to fail, ensuring more reliable UI responsiveness.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev17-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev17" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev17)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Adjusted parameters of <b>Acrylic background effect</b> for console, enhancing visual depth and clarity.
           \n- <b>Colorization strategy</b> toggle now switches between <i>default</i> and <i>wallpaper-based</i> themes, offering greater personalization.
           \n- Fixed an issue where the <b>navigation bar</b> was incorrectly displayed in areas where it should have been hidden.
           \n- Resolved a problem that caused the <b>Mini-player</b> to appear even when the <b>Console</b> was visible, ensuring a cleaner interface.
           \n- Introduced a <b>Queue Management UI</b> that intelligently adapts to screen orientation, positioning itself next to the player, similar to the YouTube application.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev18-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev18" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev18)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Integrated <b>Sleep Timer</b> functionality with a dedicated user interface and underlying logic.
           \n- Implemented <b>Playback Speed</b> controls, complete with user interface elements and operational logic.
           \n- Bug fix - Addressed an issue where removing the current track caused the player to play the first item in the queue instead of the next, improving playback continuity.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev19-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev19" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev19)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Added <b>Equalizer</b>; you can now adjust audio frequencies for a personalized listening experience.
           \n- Implemented <b>Presets</b> for the Equalizer, allowing quick selection of optimized audio settings.
           \n- Fixed an issue where the <b>Equalizer</b> settings were not consistently applied across sessions.
           \n- Resolved several minor UI bugs related to the <b>Equalizer</b> interface for a smoother user experience.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev20-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev20" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev20)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Enhanced <b>Media Management</b>: Added "Remove" and "Delete" options to the Media player screen. "Remove" takes a track out of the current playlist, while "Delete" removes it from the phone and playlist, potentially moving it to a trash folder if supported. Buttons have been updated for a better look and feel.
           \n- Smoother <b>Playback Queue</b>: Improved animation for currently playing songs in the queue.
           \n- Improved <b>New Playlist Creation</b>: The screen for creating new playlists has a refreshed look, adapts to phone orientation, features updated "Update" and "Save" buttons, and has an enhanced playlist description area.
           \n- <b>Audio Effects Screen Update</b>: The "Save" button on the audio effects screen now has a new design.
           \n- Clearer <b>Titles</b>: Updated titles on the "New Playlist" and "Audio Effects" screens for better descriptiveness.
           \n- <b>Settings Fix</b>: Resolved a minor issue with color theme settings to ensure proper functionality.
           \n- <b>Behind-the-Scenes Improvements</b>: Enhanced the functionality of the equalizer (sound settings).
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev21-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev21" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev21)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- Added MP3 <b>Tag Editor</b>: View/edit metadata (title, artist, album, etc.). Adaptive UI; Pro features for lyrics/artwork.
           \n- Refined UI in the <b>Queue</b>: the currently playing item\'s title now animates its font weight.
           \n- Adjusted the <b>Acrylic</b> effect\'s luminosity alpha in both light and dark themes for better visual balance.
           \n- Optimized <b>Image Blur Transformations</b>: Improved bitmap handling for better performance and reduced memory usage.
           \n- Enhanced <b>LazyList Placeholders</b>: Full-screen Lottie animations for loading/empty states in vertical `LazyList` components.
           \n- Streamlined <b>\"Add to Playlist\"</b>:
           \n    - New playlist selection dialog (name, track count, date, artwork). Adapts position to screen size.
           \n    - "Close" button, tap to select, placeholder for no playlists.
           \n    - Consistent dialog in Audio/Video sections. Adds tracks, filters duplicates, confirms with toast.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev22-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev22" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev22)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
           \n- <b>Save MP3 Tag Edits</b>: You can now save changes to MP3 tags with a confirmation before overwriting.
           \n- <b>MP3 Only Edits</b>: The "Edit" option now checks if a file is an MP3, showing a message if it\'s not.
           \n- <b>Add to Playlist from Videos &amp; Playlists</b>: Easily add individual videos or tracks from one playlist to another.
           \n- <b>Improved Tag Handling</b>: Better reading and writing of common ID3 tags.
           \n- <b>"Liked" Playlist Title</b>: The title for your "Liked" songs playlist is now clearer.
           \n- <b>"Recent" Playlist Update</b>: Fixed a small issue to make sure recently played items are correctly added to the "Recent" playlist.
        </font>
    </string>
    <!--v4.0.0-dev23-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev23" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev23)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
          \n- Refined <b>Console</b> UI: Streamlined dialog management and introduced dedicated state for queue visibility.
          \n- Improved <b>Sleep Timer</b> Dialog: "Start" button moved to actions slot with updated styling.
          \n- <b>Widget Overhaul</b>:
          \n    - Introduced Close button for the widget.
          \n    - <b>New FAB Video Player</b>: A new floating action button style player for video content.
          \n    - <b>Expanded Widget (MistyTunes)</b>: Added a <b>Like</b> button with a Lottie animation. Skip buttons now use `TonalIconButton` and reflect availability. "Open Console" is now a `TonalIconButton`. Footer controls layout adjusted.
          \n    - <b>Compact Widget (FabPlayer)</b>: Updated to use new request constants.
          \n- Adjusted widget padding on the Home screen for better layout when the navigation bar is not visible in portrait mode.
          \n- <b>Dynamic Feature Module Installation</b>:
          \n    - Implemented infrastructure to install dynamic feature modules (e.g., "Codex") via the Play Store.
          </font>
    </string>

    <!--v4.0.0-dev24-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev24" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev24)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
          \n- <b>New Glance-based App Widget:</b>
          \n    - Displays playback information and controls.
          \n    - Adapts layout based on size (Compact, Square, Normal).
          \n    - <b>Compact:</b> Artwork, Chronometer, Title, Play/Pause.
          \n    - <b>Square:</b> Artwork with overlaid Chronometer, Prev/Play/Pause/Next controls.
          \n    - <b>Normal:</b> Artwork, Title, Subtitle, Prev/Play/Pause/Next controls, Favourite button.
          \n    - Launches the main app on click.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--v4.0.0-dev25-->
    <string name="changelog_400_dev25" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='maroon'>(v4.0.0-dev25)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
          \n- <b>Better Media Playback:</b> Enjoy smoother playback of files opened from other apps (like your file manager), now showing correct song info and artwork.
          \n- <b>Smoother App Start:</b> Fixed issues when opening media files if the app wasn\'t already running.
          \n- <b>Real Album Art:</b> See the actual album art embedded in your music files, not just generic thumbnails. You can turn this on in settings for a richer look.
          \n- <b>Player UI Tweaks:</b> Small visual improvements in the player for clearer text and easier control access.
          \n- <b>Smaller App Size:</b> We\'ve made some internal changes to make the app a bit smaller.
          \n- <b>Consistent Look:</b> Player elements now have matching rounded corners for a cleaner design.
          \n- <b>Widget Refinement:</b> The "Like" button animation in the MistyTunes widget has been slightly adjusted for a smoother visual.
          \n- <b>Improved Background Visuals:</b> If your device doesn\'t support background blur, the Acrylic background now has a nice "frosted glass" effect, ensuring the app still looks great.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--v4.0.0-alpha01-->
    <string name="changelog_400_alpha01" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='olive'>(v4.0.0-alpha01)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
          \n- <b><u>New About Us Screen</u>:</b> App info, changelogs, other apps.
          \n- <b><u>Rate &amp; Support</u>:</b> Rate or "Buy me a coffee" via About Us.
          \n- <b><u>More Apps</u>:</b> Discover our apps in "More from Us" (About Us).
          \n- <b><u>Stay Updated</u>:</b> In-app changelog with release notes.
          \n- <b><u>Quick Links</u>:</b> Feedback, GitHub, etc. in About Us top bar.
          \n- <b><u>UI Tweaks</u>:</b> Minor layout adjustments.
          \n- <b>Revamped Settings:</b> Reorganized for easier navigation.
          \n- <b>Save Changes:</b> New "Save" button in settings for preferences.
          \n- <b>Unlock Ad-Free:</b> Clear "Unlock Ad-free" option in "Sponsor".
          \n- <b>New "Upgrades" Section:</b> Unlock premium features from settings.
          \n- <b>Consistent Styling:</b> Unified preference item appearance.
          \n- <b>Internal Improvements:</b> More efficient settings management.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--v4.0.0-alpha02-->
    <string name="changelog_400_alpha02" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='olive'>(v4.0.0-alpha02)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
          \n- <b><u>Revamped App Configuration:</u></b> We\'ve improved how app settings are managed for a more stable and efficient experience.
          \n    - Preferences for <b>Trash Can</b>, <b>Font Scale</b>, <b>Minimum Track Length</b>, <b>System Audio Effects</b>, and <b>Grid Item Size</b> are now centrally managed and reliably saved.
          \n    - We\'ve optimized the way settings are stored for better performance.
          \n- <b><u>Streamlined Settings Screen:</u></b>
          \n    - Unsaved changes are now clearly indicated, and you can easily <b>Discard Changes</b> if needed.
          \n    - Prompts for app restart (if required for settings to take effect) are now clearer.
          \n    - Navigating back from settings with unsaved changes will now prompt you to save or discard them.
          \n- <b><u>New "Acrylic Blur" Preference (Beta):</u></b> Add a stylish blur effect to backgrounds (experimental).
          \n- <b><u>Global Font Scaling:</u></b> Font size adjustments now apply consistently across the entire application.
          \n- <b><u>System Equalizer Integration:</u></b>
          \n    - If "Inbuilt Audio FX" is disabled, the Equalizer button in the player console will now attempt to launch your system\'s audio effects control panel.
          \n- <b><u>Faster Startup:</u></b> Your personalized settings are now loaded instantly when the app launches, ensuring a smooth start every time.
          \n- <b><u>Behind-the-Scenes Enhancements:</u></b> We\'ve made internal improvements for smoother animations and overall app performance.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--v4.0.0-alpha03-->
    <string name="changelog_400_alpha03" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='olive'>(v4.0.0-alpha03)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
          \n<font color='maroon'><b>Note:</b> <b>Alpha</b> release. <i>Missing features/bugs expected.</i></font>
          \n✓ <b><u>Improved Audio Effects Control:</u></b> "In-app Audio Effects" setting is now clearer. Disabling it now correctly uses your phone\'s built-in equalizer if available.
          \n✓ <b><u>Smarter Track Filtering:</u></b> Tracks shorter than your set "Minimum Track Length" (e.g., ringtones) are now properly filtered out from your music library.
          \n✓ <b><u>Refined Settings UI:</u></b>
          \n    - The "Min Track Length" slider now goes from 0 to 100 seconds in 10-second steps for easier selection.
          \n    - "Font Scale" and "Grid Item Size" sliders offer more precise adjustments with more steps.
          \n    - The "Save" button in Settings is now a Floating Action Button (FAB) for better visibility and appears only when you have pending changes.
          \n    - The app restart prompt for settings changes now uses a clearer icon and appears *before* settings are applied, so you know what to expect.
          \n✓ <b><u>Equalizer Button Logic:</u></b> The equalizer button in the player console now more reliably launches the system equalizer when in-app effects are off.
          \n✓ <b><u>New "Playback" Settings Section:</u></b> We\'ve added a dedicated section in Settings for all your playback preferences.
          \n✓ <b><u>Choose Your Video Renderer (SurfaceView vs. TextureView):</u></b>
          \n    - You can now select between `SurfaceView` (default, better performance) and `TextureView` (better for visual effects integration) for video playback. Find this in Settings > Playback > "Video Renderer".
          \n✓ <b><u>Customize FAB Player Tap Behavior:</u></b>
          \n    - Decide what happens when you tap the Floating Action Button (FAB) player:
          \n        - <b>Open Console (Default):</b> Tap opens the main player screen.
          \n        - <b>Expand to Widget:</b> Tap expands the FAB into the in-app widget.
        </font>
    </string>

    <!--v4.0.0-alpha04-->
    <string name="changelog_400_alpha04" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='olive'>(v4.0.0-alpha04)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
          \n<font color='maroon'><b>Note:</b> <b>Alpha</b> release. <i>Missing features/bugs expected.</i></font>
          \n✓ <b><u>Stream from the Web:</u></b> You can now play media directly from network URLs!
          \n    ◦ Access this new feature via a "Link" button on the Library screen.
          \n    ◦ Paste or type a URL, and we\'ll start streaming.
          \n✓ <b><u>Buffering Indicator:</u></b> The TimeBar now displays an indeterminate progress indicator when the player is buffering media.
        </font>
    </string>


    <!--v4.0.0-alpha05-->
    <string name="changelog_400_alpha05" translatable="false">
         <b>What’s New <font color='olive'>(v4.0.0-alpha06)\n</font></b>
        <font color='grey'>
            \n<font color='maroon'><b>Note:</b> <b>Alpha</b> release. <i>Missing features/bugs expected.</i></font>
            \n✓ <b><u>"Organize Files into Sections" Preference:</u></b> You can now choose to display files in library views (Albums, Audios, etc.) as a flat list or grouped into sections. Find this in Settings > General.
            \n✓ <b><u>UI Polish:</u></b>
            \n    - The <b>Close Button</b> preference and the new <b>File Grouping</b> preference in Settings now have a background color and distinct tile shapes for better visual organization.
            \n    - Increased the shadow elevation for the "Newly Added" item card and updated its shape for a more modern look.
            \n✓ <b><u>Behind-the-Scenes:</u></b>
            \n    - Removed redundant logic in <code>TimeBar</code> for handling negative progress.
            \n    - Removed accent color from "new update downloaded" snackbar message.
            \n✓ <b><u>Remove from "Recents":</u></b> Long-press an item in the "Recently Played" list on the Library screen to remove it from your history.
            \n✓ <b><u>Clearer Setting Description:</u></b> Updated the description for the "Organize Files into Sections" preference for better clarity.
        </font>
    </string>
</resources>